Office of Public Relations Records UA063
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- News releases and press kits, 1995 -- 2014; UA063.003; 6.0 Linear Feet
  - Press releases and press kits, 1995 -- 2010; UA063.003.026 (Box 26)
    Press releases; press kits; PR materials related to President Bacow and the Beyond Boundaries capital campaign; Step UP program annual reports, 2007-2011; and "Primer to the Boston Health Sciences Campus," 2005.
- Audiovisual materials, UA063.004; 3.6 Linear Feet; 21 Digital Object(s)
  This series is not arranged.
  - Banking Baby Teeth Pamela Yelick NECN, 2007; UA063.004.00001; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Banking Baby Teeth Pamela Yelick WCVB, 2007; UA063.004.00002; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - It Takes a Village Snyderman, 2007; UA063.004.00003; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Shape Up Somerville Economos, 2007; UA063.004.00004; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - NA, 2015; UA063.004.00005; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Making a World of Difference Herman Kugel, 2007; UA063.004.00006; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Fit Town Economos, 2007; UA063.004.00007; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Exercise and the Brain Nelson, 2007; UA063.004.00008; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Calcium Vitamin D and Fractures DawsonHughes, 2006; UA063.004.00009; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Antibacterial Resistance and Probiotics Levy Goldin, 2006; UA063.004.00010; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - The Danger of Antibiotics in Livestock Feed, 2009; UA063.004.00011; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Kentucky Derby Winner Barbaro Breaks Leg, 2006; UA063.004.00012; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - The Connection with Peter Walker, 2005; UA063.004.00013; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Early Detection, 2007; UA063.004.00014; 7 Digital Object(s)
  - Nutrition and Genomics Media Conference, 2001; UA063.004.00015; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Infected, 2008; UA063.004.00016; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - War on Fat, 2006; UA063.004.00017; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Faster, Higher Farther: Older Athletes Defy Limits, 2008; UA063.004.00018; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Teeth Whitening, 2008; UA063.004.00019; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Nutrition Science, 2007; UA063.004.00020; 34 Digital Object(s)
  - L'aventure antibiotique Episode I, 2008; UA063.004.00021; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Recordings of Health Sciences events and faculty media appearances, UA063.004.027 (Box data_value_missing_b946e7545a4d1b7b626865c8db32f2a9, Box 27)
- Additional accessions, UA063.000348
  - Student information cards, UA063-001 (Box data_value_missing_feb8c00ec53b2ecd7c7cbb2c128efa15, Box 1)
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - HNRCA Photo Book and Nutrition and Genomics conference binder and press releases, 1981 -- 2001; UA063-002 (Box 3, Box 2)